Milos Vasic, curriculum vitae



About

Milos Vasic is highly-skilled software engineer bringing years in software design, development, and integration. Advanced knowledge of Android, React Native and Flutter. Main programming languages: Java, Kotlin, Dart, TypeScript and C++. Experienced in the full project life cycle from design to implementation to integration.

- E-Mail: i@mvasic.ru
- Mobile: +381 69 25 35 718 (Serbia), +7 966 323 77 17 (Russian Federation)
- Language: Serbian, English, Russian.
- Source code and Open-Source: GitHub, GitFlic
- Telegram: milos85vasic
- Networks: Linkedin, TenChat, Xing, VK
- Some of the Open-Source work: Mail Server Factory, Android Toolkit, HelixTrack

Education

- Bachelor of Science: Informatics and Computing, 2008. University Singidunum, Belgrade (Serbia)
- M.Sc: Contemporary Information Technologies, 2014. University Singidunum, Belgrade (Serbia)

Technology

Using the following technology:

• Android, JetPack Compose, MVVP, Retrofit, OkHttp, Firebase, etc.

- React Native, Expo, Npm, Yarn
- Flutter
- Kotlin, Kotlin Coroutines, Java, Swift, Dart, JavaScript, TypeScript, C++
- Also: Python, Ruby, Bash, Go, iOS, QT
- Additional: Docker, Docker Compose,
- Sqlite, Postgres, MongoDB, Redis
- Linux, macOS

Experience

Through the career have been working on the various projects and with various clients.

- Harness Belgrade, Serbia (full-time), from 03/2020 until 12/2024, Staff software engineer
- Leica Geosystems Heerbrugg, Switzerland (full-time), from 02/2016 until 02/2020, Android and iOS developer
- Bosch Belgrade, Serbia (full-time), from 01/2010 until 01/2016, Android SDK developer